{
    "subject": "resource/Bronze_Head_of_Hypnos_from_Civitella_d'Arna",
    "predicate": "property/registration",
    "object": "GR 1868.6-6.9",
    "human_readable": "The Bronze Head of Hypnos from Civitella d'Arna is registered as GR 1868.6-6.9.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9099615812301636,
            "question": "What is the registration number of The Bronze Head of Hypnos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8917774558067322,
            "question": "Where is The Bronze Head of Hypnos from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8420854806900024,
            "question": "What material is The Bronze Head of Hypnos made from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7713355422019958,
            "question": "Where can I find more information about The Bronze Head of Hypnos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7647354602813721,
            "question": "Is there any information about the artist who created The Bronze Head of Hypnos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.734964907169342,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the artistic style of The Bronze Head of Hypnos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7286926507949829,
            "question": "What is the significance of The Bronze Head of Hypnos in art history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7057878375053406,
            "question": "What period does The Bronze Head of Hypnos likely belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6918808817863464,
            "question": "Are there any similar sculptures or artifacts that could be related to The Bronze Head of Hypnos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48595568537712097,
            "question": "Who is Hypnos?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Bronze Head of Hypnos from Civitella d'Arna is registered as GR 1868.6-6.9.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2384_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any similar sculptures or artifacts that could be related to The Bronze Head of Hypnos?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2384_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What period does The Bronze Head of Hypnos likely belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2384_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of The Bronze Head of Hypnos in art history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2384_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2384_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2384_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2384_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2384_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2384_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2384_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2384_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2384_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2384_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2384_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n`{'output': 'no'}`\n\nThe reason is that there is no mention in the documents about the Bronze Head of Hypnos being registered as GR 1868.6-6.9, but rather it was purchased by the British Museum along with other parts of the Castellani Collection in 1868 (see file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2384/re-ranker-msmarco/51.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: None of the provided documents contain information about a registration number for the Bronze Head of Hypnos from Civitella d'Arna being registered as GR 1868.6-6.9. The documents describe the provenance and some details about the sculpture but do not provide this specific registration detail."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information in the context provided that supports the registration number GR 1868.6-6.9 for the Bronze Head of Hypnos from Civitella d'Arna.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}